

# Azzam Syakir

+62 812 8146 6127 | azzamsykir@gmail.com

### **About Me**

Hello! I'm Azzam Syakir, a seasoned Backend Developer with 5 years of programming expertise. I have experience with various software architecture implementations, including Clean Architecture, Micro-services, MVVM, and MVC patterns. With 2 years in Golang and 1 year in Laravel, I excel in creating clean, scalable systems. Check out my diverse projects on GitHub: <u>AzzamSyakir</u>. Let's innovate together!

### **Education**

(2019-2022) | Quadrant Boarding school | IT School

I studied at Quadrant Boarding School, an IT-focused school, from 2019 to 2022, where I learned programming and focused on backend development.

### (2022-present) | HomeSchool HighSchool

I am continuing my high school education at HomeSchool HighSchool from 2022 to the present.

## **Working Experience**

### February 2024 - Present | golang backend freelance • Freelancer.com

As a freelance Golang Backend Developer, I leverage Golang to create innovative and impactful solutions. My programming expertise and experience in backend development ensure high-quality, efficient, and scalable results tailored to each client's needs.

### January 2024 - Present | golang backend freelance • Upwork

As a freelance Golang Backend Developer, I leverage Golang to create innovative and impactful solutions. My programming expertise and experience in backend development ensure high-quality, efficient, and scalable results tailored to each client's needs.

#### **Skills**

Programming Languages:

• Golang, PHP/Laravel, Python/Django, Java/Spring Boot

Other Skills:

- Backend development (4 years experience), Microservices & Clean Architecture, SQL & NoSQL Databases, REST API & gRPC, Testing Cloud:
- AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, GCP, Redis

languages:

-Indonesia-Native

English-intermediate